Boyars mss., 1960-2010 LMC 2953
Lilly Library
- Publishing Files
  - Collins, Warwick
    - Challenge - typescript (Vol. II), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Conrad, Borys
    - Author file, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - von Conta, Manfred
    - The Deathbringer - cover proof, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cook, Raymond
    - The China Years - cover proofs, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The China Years - reviews, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Copland, Aaron & Vivian Perlis
    - Copland since 1943 - cover drafts, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Copland since 1943 - correspondence and files, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Cortazar, Julio
    - Cronopios & Famas - cover drafts, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cronopios & Famas - correspondence and files, 1978-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Cronopios & Famas - cover proofs, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Cronopios and Famas - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 62: A Model Kit - cover proofs, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 62: A Model Kit - correspondence and files, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 62: A Model Kit - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - All Fires the Fire - cover proofs, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - All Fires the Fire - correspondence and files, 1977-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - All Fires the Fire - cover drafts, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - All Fires the Fire - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1969-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Cousin, Gabriel
    - Black Opera and The Girl who Barks like a Dog - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Creeley, Robert
    - Later - correspondence and files, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Later - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - The Finger - correspondence and files, 1970-1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Finger - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - The Gold Diggers - correpsondence and files, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Windows - correspondence and files, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Windows - reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Collected Prose - reviews, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Collected Prose - cover proofs, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Collected Prose - correspondence and files, 1983-1990 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
    - Collected Prose - artwork, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Collected Prose - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Echoes - correspondence and files, 1995? (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Echoes - page proofs, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Echoes - reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Memory Gardens - correspondence and files, 1987? (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Memory Gardens - reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Selected Poems - correspondence and files, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Selected Poems - reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Selected Poems - cover proofs, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Collected Poems - reviews, 1984-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Life & Death - correspondence and files, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Life & Death - reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hello: A Journal - cover proofs, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Hello: A Journal - correspondence and files, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Hello: A Journal - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - The Charm - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Reviews and publicity, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Author file, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
  - Cunningham, Merce
    - The Dancer and the Dance - reviews and publicity, 1985-2000 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - The Dancer and the Dance - cover drafts, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - The Dancer and the Dance - typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - The Dancer and the Dance - page proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
    - The Dancer and the Dance - correspondence and files, 1984-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5-8)
    - The Dancer and the Dance - artwork, undated (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
    - The Dancer and the Dance - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Dahlberg, Edward
    - The Sorrows of Priapus - page proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - The Sorrows of Priapus - reviews, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Dalos, Gyorgy
    - The Circumcision - cover proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - The Circumcision - reviews, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dalton, David
    - Janis: Piece of my Heart - reviews, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Janis: Piece of my Heart - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
  - Daniel, Yuli
    - Prison Poems - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
  - Davys, Sarah
    - A Time & A Time - cover proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - de Falla, Manuel
    - On Music and Musicians - correspondence and files, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - On Music and Musicians - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Death, Sarah
    - Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Dickson, Paul
    - The Electronic Battlefield - correspondence and files, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - The Electronic Battlefield - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - van Dieren, Wouter
    - Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - van Dieren, Wouter & Marius G. W. Hummelinck
    - Nature's Price - correspondence and files, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Nature's Price - page proofs, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Nature's Price - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Dolto, Francoise
    - Flower Dolls - correspondence and files, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Dorfman, Ariel
    - Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Drieu la Rochelle, Pierre
    - Will O' the Wisp - cover proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Will O' the Wisp - reviews, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Will O' the Wisp - correspondence and files, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Will O' the Wisp - page proofs, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Dumont, Rene
    - Growth of Hunger - correspondence and files, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Growth of Hunger - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
  - du Preez, Wilhelmus Petrus
    - Genocide - correspondence and files, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Durgnat, Raymond
    - Eros in the Cinema - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Echols, Alice
    - Scars of Sweet Paradise - reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Edvardson, Cordelia
    - Buried Child Seeks the Fire - draft, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Edwards, Gwynne
    - Indecent Exposures - reviews, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Indecent Exposures - cover proofs, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Indecent Exposures - correspondence and files, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
    - Indecent Exposures - typescript, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
    - Lorca: The Theatre Beneath the Sand - cover drafts, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Lorca: The Theatre Beneath the Sand - cover proofs, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Lorca: The Theatre Beneath the Sand - correspondence and files, 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
    - Lorca: The Theatre Beneath the Sand - reviews, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Lorca: The Theatre Beneath the Sand - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Burning the Curtain - typescripts, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - The Discreet Art of Luis Bunuel - cover proofs, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - The Discreet Art of Luis Bunuel - cover draft, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - The Discreet Art of Luis Bunuel - reviews, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - The Discreet Art of Luis Bunuel - correspondence and files, 1982-1991 (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
    - The Discreet Art of Luis Bunuel - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Edwards, Page
    - Touring - correspondence and files, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Mules that Angels Ride - reviews, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Staking Claims - reviews, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Staking Claims - page proofs, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Staking Claims - correspondence and files, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Crabbe's Retreat - typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The Search for Kate Duval - reviews, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - The Lake - reviews, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Peggy Salte - reviews, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - American Girl - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Erikson, Erik H.
    - Toys & Reasons - cover proofs, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Toys & Reasons - correspondence and files, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Ewen, Frederic
    - Bertolt Brecht - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Faldbakken, Knut
    - Author file, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Faure, Gabriel
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Gabriel Faure: His Life Through His Letters - cover proofs (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Fayyad, Soleyman
    - Voices - cover drafts, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Voices - correspondence and files, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Feinstein, Elaine
    - The Border - reviews, 1984-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - The Border - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Figgis, Paddy
    - On the Bright Road - reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - On the Bright Road - correspondence and files, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - On the Bright Road - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Finnegan, Seamus
    - The Cemetery of Europe - reviews, 1986-1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - The Cemetery of Europe - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - North - cover drafts, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - North - correspondence and files, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - North - reviews, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - North - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Fisher, Seymour
    - Body Consciousness - reviews, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Body Consciousness - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Fletcher, John
    - Novel & Reader - correspondence and files, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Novel & Reader - reviews, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Novel & Reader - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Claude Simon and Fiction Now - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Foster, Paul
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Freely, Maureen
    - Enlightenment - reviews, 2006-2008 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Enlightenment - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Frobenius, Nikolas
    - De Sade's Valet - reviews, 1997-2002 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - De Sade's Valet - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Fuks, Ladislav
    - The Cremator - correspondence and files, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - The Cremator - reviews, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Fyfe, Mark
    - Asher - reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Asher - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Gadol, Peter
    - Light at Dusk - reviews, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Light at Dusk - cover proofs, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Gangemi, Kenneth
    - OLT - correspondence and files, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Interceptor Pilot - correspondence and files, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Interceptor Pilot - reviews, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Interceptor Pilot - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Publicity, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Author file, 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 41-43)
    - Various drafts and typescripts, undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Gebler, Carlo
    - W9 and Other Lives - reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - W9 and Other Lives - correspondence and files, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Father & I - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Father & I - correspondence and files, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Father & I - reviews, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - How to Murder a Man - reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - How to Murder a Man - correspondence and files, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Gill, Peter
    - Small Change & Kick for Touch - reviews, 1984-2008 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Small Change & Kick for Touch - cover proofs and artwork, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Small Change & Kick for Touch - correspondence and files, 1984-2008 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Author file, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Gillieron, Rebecca and Catheryn Kilgarriff
    - The Bookaholic's Guide to Book Blogs - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Gombrowicz, Witold
    - Pornografia - reviews, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Pornografia - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - A Kind of Testament - correspondence and files, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - A Kind of Testament - reviews, 1988-1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - A Kind of Testament - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Three Plays - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Three Plays - correspondence and files, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Three Plays - reviews, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Ferdydurke - correspondence and files, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Ferdydurke - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Ferdydurke - reviews, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Ferdydurke - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Princess Ivona - reviews, 1988-1998 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Princess Ivona - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Possessed - reviews, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Possessed - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Possessed - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Operetta - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - The Marriage - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Goodman, David S. G.
    - Beijing Street Voices - cover proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Beijing Street Voices - reviews, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Beijing Street Voices - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Goulet, Robert
    - Madhouse - reviews, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Green, Julien
    - Stars of the South - correspondence and files, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 34-35)
    - Stars of the South - reviews, 1990-1997 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Dixie - reviews, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - "'Out of Space, Out of Time': The Virginia Novels of Julien Green", 2006 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Christine & Other Stories - xerox, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Love in America - reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Love in America - correspondence and files, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Love in America - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - The Green Paradise - cover drafts, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - The Green Paradise - correspondence and files, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - The Green Paradise - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - The War at Sixteen - reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The War at Sixteen - correspondence and files, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Varouna - typescript and xerox, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Distant Lands - correspondence and files, 1987-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11-15)
    - The Distant Lands - reviews, 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Paris - correspondence and files, 1991-2004 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
    - Paris - reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Paris - cover proofs, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - South - reviews, 1991-1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - South - correspondence and files, 1991-1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - South - cover proofs, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - If I Were You - xerox, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - L'Etudiant Roux - typescript, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Restless Youth - reviews, 1966-1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Restless Youth - correspondence and files, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Restless Youth - typescript (3 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 5-9)
    - Restless Youth - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - The Apprentice Writer - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Greenfield, Howard
    - The Devil & Dr. Barnes - correspondence and files, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The Devil & Dr. Barnes - reviews, 1987-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The Devil & Dr. Barnes - cover drafts and artwork, 1996? (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The Devil & Dr. Barnes - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1989-1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Greenslade, Roy
    - Goodbye to the Working Class - correspondence and files, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Goodbye to the Working Class - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Grieg, Edvard
    - Grieg & Delius- correspondence and files, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Griffiths, Gareth
    - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - A Double Exile - correspondence and files, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - A Double Exile - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Gyllensten, Lars
    - The Testament of Cain - xerox, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Haff, Bergljot Hobaek
    - The Price of Purity - typescript, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Hartenfels, Jerome
    - Lazarus - reviews, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Lazarus - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Doctor Death - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Hatziyannidis, Vangelis
    - Four Walls - reviews, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Stolen Time - reviews, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Havekamp, Katharina
    - Love Comes in Buckets - correspondence and files, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Heath, Roy
    - Kwaku - cover proofs, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Kwaku - reviews, 1982-1997 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Reviews, 1988-1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Heilbroner, Robert L.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - An Inquiry into the Human Prospect - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Beyond Boom and Crash - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Business Civilization in Decline - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Heissenbuttel, Helmut
    - Texts - correspondence and files, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Texts - cover proofs, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Texts - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Hemming, James
    - Instead of God - reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Instead of God - correspondence and files, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Instead of God - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - The Betrayal of Youth - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1980-1997 (Box 15, Folder 9-11)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Hennig, Margaret
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Henry, Faith
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Herburger, Gunter
    - Monotonous Landscape - reviews, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Hiquily, Arlene Colombe
    - Memoirs of the Frog Prince - reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Memoirs of the Frog Prince - page proofs, undated (Box 15, Folder 17-18)
    - Memoirs of the Frog Prince - page proofs (incomplete), undated (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
    - Memoirs of the Frog Prince - photocopy, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Memoirs of the Frog Prince - annotated typescript, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Memoirs of the Frog Prince - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hoch, Paul
    - The Newspaper Game - reviews, 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Hocquenghem, Guy
    - Eve - typescript, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Eve - reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Holland, Patricia
    - Images of Childhood - typescript and artwork, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Hollander, David
    - L.I.E. - cover proofs, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - L.I.E. - correspondence and files, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - L.I.E. - reviews, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Hollings, Ken
    - Destroy All Monsters - cover proofs, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Destroy All Monsters - correspondence and files, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Destroy All Monsters - reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hollington, Michael
    - Gunter Grass - correspondence and files, 1979-1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Gunter Grass - reviews, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Gunter Grass - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Hopkins, John
    - The Great Years - typescript, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
  - Horsley, Jake
    - Dogville vs. Hollywood - cover proofs, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Dogville vs. Hollywood - reviews, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Howell, Anthony
    - Oslo - reviews, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Oslo - cover proofs, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - In the Company of Others - reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - In the Company of Others - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Three Novellas - typescript, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Peire & Lunete - typescript, undated (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Hummelinck, M. G. Wagenaar
    - Photographs, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Hungerford, Carole
    - The Good Body Guide - reviews, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Hyde, G. M.
    - Vladimir Nabokov - correspondence and files, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Illich, Ivan
    - Gender - correspondence and files, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Gender - cover proofs, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Gender - page proofs, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Gender - reviews and publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Gender - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Disabling Professions - cover drafts, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Disabling Professions - correspondence and files, 1977-1998 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Disabling Professions - cover proofs, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Disabling Professions - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - ABC - cover drafts, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - ABC - correspondence and files, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - ABC - reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - ABC - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Energy and Equity - correspondence and files, 1974-1979 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
    - Shadow Work - correspondence and files, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Shadow Work - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - H2O and the Waters of Forgetfulness - correspondence and files, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - H2O and the Waters of Forgetfulness - cover proofs, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - H2O and the Waters of Forgetfulness - reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - In the Mirror of the Past - reviews, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - In the Mirror of the Past - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - In the Vineyard of the Text - typescript, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Deschooling Society - reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Deschooling Society - cover proofs, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)